flutterclub.com 2013-11-04

# Flutterclub - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

**PLEASE REVIEW THE FOLLOWING NOTICE PRIOR TO SUBMITTING ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIS WEBSITE.**

Social Gaming Ventures Ltd ('SGV') processes personal information submitted by you on the flutterclub.com site ('the Site') in accordance with all applicable data protection and privacy laws. This privacy statement is to be read in conjunction with the site [Terms & Conditions](http://www.flutterclub.com/fc/help/terms). Where you decide to register on this Site we will use the personal information or data that you provide in the following manner:

  * for the purposes of processing of setting up and maintaining your account;
  * running competitions;
  * where you have indicated that you wish to receive marketing correspondence we will use your data to send you such correspondence. We may also contact you about your account status.

You are also free at any time to ask us to provide you with a copy of the personal information that we hold on you and/or to correct and/or to delete all or any part your personal information from our records. Such a request should be in writing and addressed to Social Gaming Ventures Ltd, Gandon Chambers, 3 Farmhill Road, Clonskeagh, Dublin 14.

You are responsible for ensuring that the personal data relating to you, held by us is accurate and kept up-to-date at all times. Personal information submitted by you as set out above shall be held by us for no longer than is necessary. If the personal information relating to you that we hold is out-of-date please let us know by emailing us on info@flutterclub.com.

SGV may also gather anonymous information, which may be used by SGV or shared with third parties. This information does not personally identify you but may be helpful for improving the services we offer. Generally this information is collected through 'traffic data' and may entail the use of 'cookies,' 'IP addresses', or other numeric codes used to identify a computer.

'Cookies' give users a special, random ID that are small text files, which are stored on the hard drive of a user's computer. SGV employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges for certain locations on the Site. You may deactivate cookies by adjusting the settings on your Internet browser.

SGV may perform statistical analysis of user behaviour in order to measure interest in the Site and to inform third parties as to how many users have clicked on links to third party websites, advertisements and/or banners. In this statistical analysis, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. Personal information about you as an individual will not be provided to any third party except as described herein.
